[
  {
    "type": "intro",
    "pretext": "You learned that characters modified with dakuten and handakuten can also be written with “ャ,” “ュ,” and “ョ”. Take this short quiz! But first, let’s review:"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "G and J",
    "options": [
      "Gya – ギャ",
      "Gyu – ギュ",
      "Gyo – ギョ",
      "Ja – ジャ",
      "Ju – ジュ",
      "Jo – ジョ"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "B and P",
    "options": [
      "Bya – ビャ",
      "Byu – ビュ",
      "Byo – ビョ",
      "Pya – ピャ",
      "Pyu – ピュ",
      "Pyo – ピョ"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Gyo",
    "options": ["ギョ", "ギャ", "ギュ"],
    "answer": "ギョ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Gyu",
    "options": ["ギャ", "ギョ", "ギュ"],
    "answer": "ギュ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Gya",
    "options": ["ギョ", "ギュ", "ギャ"],
    "answer": "ギャ"
  },
  {"type": "mc", "prompt": "Ja", "options": ["ジュ", "ジャ", "ジョ"], "answer": "ジャ"},
  {"type": "mc", "prompt": "Jo", "options": ["ジョ", "ジュ", "ジャ"], "answer": "ジョ"},
  {"type": "mc", "prompt": "Ju", "options": ["ジョ", "ジュ", "ジャ"], "answer": "ジュ"},
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Byo",
    "options": ["ビャ", "ビュ", "ビョ"],
    "answer": "ビョ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Bya",
    "options": ["ビョ", "ビャ", "ビュ"],
    "answer": "ビャ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Byu",
    "options": ["ビュ", "ビョ", "ビャ"],
    "answer": "ビュ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Pyo",
    "options": ["ピャ", "ピョ", "ピュ"],
    "answer": "ピョ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Pyu",
    "options": ["ピュ", "ピョ", "ピャ"],
    "answer": "ピュ"
  },
  {"type": "mc", "prompt": "Pya", "options": ["ピョ", "ピュ", "ピャ"], "answer": "ピャ"}
]